Guide to the Ted Fagan Collection
Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound
- Reel to reel tapes
  - Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Rosenkavalier. Part IDec. 22, 1962, 10" reel (Box 33, Folder 806)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXIV) Crespin, Régine, soprano; Rothenberger, Anneliese, soprano; Töpper, Hertha, mezzo-soprano. Metropolitan Opera Orchestra. Maazel, Lorin, 1930-, conductor
  - Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Rosenkavalier. Part IIDec. 22, 1962, 10" reel (Box 33, Folder 807)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXV) Crespin, Régine, soprano; Rothenberger, Anneliese, soprano; Töpper, Hertha, mezzo-soprano. Metropolitan Opera Orchestra. Maazel, Lorin, 1930-, conductor
  - Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Rosenkavalier. Part IIIDec. 22, 1962, 10" reel (Box 33, Folder 808)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXVI) Crespin, Régine, soprano; Rothenberger, Anneliese, soprano; Töpper, Hertha, mezzo-soprano. Metropolitan Opera Orchestra. Maazel, Lorin, 1930-, conductor
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Ballo in maschera. Part II Jan. 12, 1963, 10" reel (Box 33, Folder 809)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXVII. Continued from tape 449) Tucker, Richard, 1913-1975, tenor; Nilsson, Birgit, soprano; Merrill, Robert, 1917-2004, baritone; Madeira, Jean, contralto; Dobbs, Mattiwilda, soprano. Metropolitan Oera Orchestra. Santi, Nello, conductor
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Rigoletto, 10" reel (Box 33, Folder 810)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXVIII) Sutherland, Joan, 1926-, soprano; Cioni, Renato, tenor; Siepi, Cesare, bass; McNeil; Crena
  - Young People's Concerts. Bernstein, Leonard, 1918-1990 Jan. 15, 1963, 10" reel (Box 33, Folder 811)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXIX) Television broadcast Weiner, Joan, piano; Hoca, Claudia, piano; Paul, Pamela, piano. Each play a movement of the concerto. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Concertos, piano, orchestra, K. 488, A major -- Watts, Andre, piano. Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886. Concertos, piano, orchestra, no. 1, E? major. Bernstein, Leonard, 1918-1990. conductor
  - Menotti, Gian Carlo, 1911-2007. Labyrinth. World TV premiere. March 3, 1963, 10" reel (Box 33, Folder 812)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXX) Tape missing Raskin, Judith as the bride; Reardon, John, 1930-1988 as the bridegroom; Bonazzi, Elaine as the spy; White, Robert as the chess player; Wolff, Beverly as the executive director; Poretta, Frank as the astronaut; Lishner, Leon, 1913-1995 as death. Grossman, Herbert, 1934-, conductor
  - Jenny Lind sings; Richard Wagner conducts, 10" reel (Box 33, Folder 813)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXXI) Lind, Jenny, 1820-1887, soprano. Bellini, Vincenzo, 1801-1835. Sonnambula. Ah! non giunge. Recorded in 1883 -- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tristan und Isolde. Recorded in 1880. Act II. Wagner, Richard, conductor
  - Young People's Concerts. Bernstein, Leonard, 1918-1990, 10" reel (Box 33, Folder 814)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXXII) Fernández, Oscar Lorenzo, 1897-1948. Reisado do pastoreio. Batuque -- Davrath, Netania, soprano. Villa-Lobos, Heitor. Bachianas brasileiras, no. 5 -- Revueltas, Silvestre, 1899-1940. Sensemayá -- Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990. Danzón cubano
  - Scarlatti, Alessandro, 1660-1725. Trionfo dell'onore, 10" reel (Box 33, Folder 815)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXXIII)
  - Lenya, Lotte reads Brecht, Bertolt, 1898-1956. Kinderkreuzzug 1939, 10" reel (Box 33, Folder 816)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXXIV)
  - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Ascanio in Alba, 10" reel (Box 33, Folder 817)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXXV)
  - Delius, Frederick, 1862-1934. Sea drift. Delius Society Series, 10" reel (Box 33, Folder 818)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXXVI) Henderson, Roy, baritone. Beecham, Thomas, Sir, 1879-1961, conductor
  - Callas, Maria, 1923-1977, 10" reel (Box 34, Folder 819)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXXVII) Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Carmen. Selections -- Interview with Weaver, William, in Europe.
  - Bayreuth traditional Wagner, 10" reel (Box 34, Folder 820)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXXVIII)
  - Berlioz, Hector, 1803-1869. Béatrice et Bénédict, 10" reel (Box 34, Folder 821)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXXIX)
  - Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Firebird. Suite (1945)., 10" reel (Box 34, Folder 822)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXXX) Szell, George, 1897-1970, conductor
  - Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Lucrezia Borgia. Part I, 10" reel (Box 34, Folder 823)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXXXI) Caballé, Montserrat, soprano; Vanzo, Alain, tenor; Perlea, Jonel, conductor. United States debut
  - Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Lucrezia Borgia. Part II, 10" reel (Box 34, Folder 824)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXXXII) Caballé, Montserrat, soprano; Vanzo, Alain, tenor; Perlea, Jonel, conductor. United States debut
  - Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich, 1840-1893. Pique dame. Part IJan. 15, 1966, 10" reel (Box 34, Folder 825)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXXXIII) Madeira, Jean as the old countess; McCracken, James as Gherman; Stratas, Teresa as Lisa; Cassel, Walter as Count Tomsky; Elias, Rosalind as Pauline; Walker, William as Prince Yeletsky. Metropolitan OperaOrchestra. Schippers, Thomas, conductor
  - Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich, 1840-1893. Pique dame. Part IIJan. 15, 1966, 10" reel (Box 34, Folder 826)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXXXIV) Madeira, Jean as the old countess; McCracken, James as Gherman; Stratas, Teresa as Lisa; Cassel, Walter as Count Tomsky; Elias, Rosalind as Pauline; Walker, William as Prince Yeletsky. Metropolitan OperaOrchestra. Schippers, Thomas, conductor
  - Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Italiana in Algeri Jan. 15, 1966, 10" reel (Box 34, Folder 827)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXXXV)
  - Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Walküre. Act II Jan. 15, 1966, 10" reel (Box 34, Folder 828)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXXXVI) Winkler, Hermann, tenor. Walter, Bruno, 1876-1962, conductor
  - Mahler, Gustav, 1860-1911. Knaben Wunderhorn, 10" reel (Box 34, Folder 829)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXXXVII. Taped from discs) Poell, Alfred, 1900-1968, tenor; Sydney, Lorna, mezzo-soprano. Wiener Staatsoper. Prohaska, Felix, conductor
  - Austral, Florence, 1894-1968, soprano, 10" reel (Box 34, Folder 830)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXXXVIII. Taped from discs)
  - Falla, Manuel de, 1876-1946. Noches en los jardines de Espana Apr. 1, 1957, 10" reel (Box 34, Folder 831)
    (Fagan's original numbering CLXXXIX. Mother tape) Novaes, Guiomar, piano
  - Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Messiah. Part I, 10" reel (Box 34, Folder 832)
    (Fagan's original numbering CXC. ) Davis, Colin, 1927-, conductor
  - Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Messiah. Part II, 10" reel (Box 34, Folder 833)
    (Fagan's original numbering CXCI) Davis, Colin, 1927-, conductor
  - International Concert Hall, 10" reel (Box 34, Folder 834)
    (Fagan's original numbering CXCII) De Vito, Gioconda, violin; Galli, viola. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Sinfonie concertanti, violin, viola, orchestra, K. 364, E? major. Radiotelevisione italiana. Orchestra sinfonica di Torino. Rossi, Mario, conductor -- Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Prélude à l'après-midi d'un faune. Concertgebouworkest. Rosbaud, Hans, 1895-1962, conductor -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Concertos, pianos (3), string orchestra, D minor; Casadesus, Robert, 1899-1972, piano; Casadesus, Gaby, piano; Casadesus, Jean, 1927-1972, piano. Belgian Chamber Orchestra
  - Levy, Marvin David. Mourning becomes Electra. World premiere. Part I. April 1, 1967, 10" reel (Box 34, Folder 835)
    (Fagan's original numbering CXCIII) Collier, Marie as Christine Mannon; Lear, Evelyn as Lavinia Mannon; Michalski, Raymond as Jed; Milnes, Sherrill as Adam Brant; Böttcher, Ronald as Peter Niles; Sukis, Lilian as Helen Niles; Macurdy, John as Ezra Mannon; Reardon, John as Orin Mannon. Metropolitan Opera Ortchestra. Mehta, Zubin, conductor
  - Levy, Marvin David. Mourning becomes Electra. World premiere. Part II. April 1, 1967, 10" reel (Box 35, Folder 836)
    (Fagan's original numbering CXCIV) Collier, Marie as Christine Mannon; Lear, Evelyn as Lavinia Mannon; Michalski, Raymond as Jed; Milnes, Sherrill as Adam Brant; Böttcher, Ronald as Peter Niles; Sukis, Lilian as Helen Niles; Macurdy, John as Ezra Mannon; Reardon, John as Orin Mannon. Metropolitan Opera Ortchestra. Mehta, Zubin, conductor
  - Lenya, Lotte. Camera three (Television program), 10" reel (Box 35, Folder 837)
    (Fagan's original numbering CXCV)
  - Turina, Joaquín, 1882-1949. Canto a Sevilla, 10" reel (Box 35, Folder 838)
    (Fagan's original numbering CXCVI. Taped from discs)
  - Villa-Lobos, Heitor. Bachianas brasileiras, no. 2, 5, 6, 9, 10" reel (Box 35, Folder 839)
    (Fagan's original numbering CXCVII. Taped from discs)
  - Vaughan Williams and Rimsky-Korsakov, 10" reel (Box 35, Folder 840)
    (Fagan's original numbering CXCVIII. Taped from discs) Vaughan Williams, Ralph, 1872-1958. Mass, G minor -- Rimsky-Korsakov, Nikolay, 1844-1908. Sadko (Opera); Rimsky-Korsakov, Nikolay, 1844-1908. Noch' pered Rozhdestvom. Suite
  - Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Images, orchestra, 10" reel (Box 35, Folder 841)
    (Fagan's original numbering CIC)
  - Wiener Festwochen. Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Messa da Requiem 1963, 10" reel (Box 35, Folder 842)
    (Fagan's original numbering CC) Lorengar, Pilar, soprano; Ludwig, Christa, contralto; Gedda, Nicolai, tenor; Ghiaurov, Nicolai, 1929-2004, bass. Berliner Rundfunk. Sinfonie-Orchester. Maazel, Lorin, 1930-, conductor. Wiener Singverein. Gillesberger, Hans, conductor
  - Sutherland, Joan, 1926-, soprano and Elkins, Margreta, mezzo-soprano Oct. 6, 1963, 10" reel (Box 35, Folder 843)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCI) Television broadcast. Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880. Belle Hélène. Overture. London Symphony Orchestra. Bonynge, Richard, conductor -- Meyerbeer, Giacomo, 1791-1864. Huguenots. O beau pays -- Bellini, Vincenzo, 1801-1835. Norma. Mira, o Norma -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Traviata. Addio del passato -- Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Linda di Chamounix. Selection; Lucia di Lammermoor. Dolce suono
  - Mahler, Gustav, 1860-1911. Symphonies, no. 2, C minor. In memoriam Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963 Nov. 24, 1963, 10" reel (Box 35, Folder 844)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCII) Television broadcast Tourel, Jennie, soprano; Amara, Lucine, soprano. New York Philharmonic. Bernstein, Leonard, 1918-1990
  - Vocal Selections, 10" reel (Box 35, Folder 845)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCIII. Taped from discs)
  - Bernstein, Leonard, 1918-1990. Kaddish. Boston premiere Feb. 8, 1964, 10" reel (Box 35, Folder 846)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCIV) Bernstein, Felicia, speaker; Tourel, Jennie, soprano
  - Menotti, Gian Carlo, 1911-2007. Ultimo selvaggio, 10" reel (Box 35, Folder 847)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCV) Radio Broadcast London, George, 1920-1985 as Abdul; Peters, Roberta, 1930- as Kitty; Gedda, Nicolai. as Kodanda; Stratas, Teresa as Sardula; Flagello, Ezio as the Maharajah; Chookasian, Lili as the Maharanee; Meredith, Morley as Mr. Scattergood. Metropolitan Opera Orchestra. Schippers, Thomas, conductor
  - Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963. Concerto, organ & string orchestra, G minor., 10" reel (Box 35, Folder 848)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCVI) Radio Broadcast
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Falstaff. Part II March 21, 1964, 10" reel (Box 35, Folder 849)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCVII) First part in tape No.511 Colzani, Anselmo as Sir John Falstaff; Tucci, Gabriella as Alice Ford; Sereni, Mario as Ford; Resnik, Regina, 1922- as Dame Quickly; Alva, Luigi as Fenton; Raskin, Judith as Nannetta; Elias, Rosalind as Meg Page. Metropolitan Opera Orchestra. Bernstein, Leonard, 1918-1990, conductor.
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Falstaff. Part III March 21, 1964, 10" reel (Box 35, Folder 850)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCVIII) First part in tape No.511 Colzani, Anselmo as Sir John Falstaff; Tucci, Gabriella as Alice Ford; Sereni, Mario as Ford; Resnik, Regina, 1922- as Dame Quickly; Alva, Luigi as Fenton; Raskin, Judith as Nannetta; Elias, Rosalind as Meg Page. Metropolitan Opera Orchestra. Bernstein, Leonard, 1918-1990, conductor.
  - Lute Music of the ElizabethansMarch 21, 1964, 10" reel (Box 35, Folder 851)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCIX. Taped from discs) Bream, Julian, lute
  - Mahler, Gustav, 1860-1911. Symphonies, no. 3, D minor March 21, 1964, 10" reel (Box 36, Folder 852)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCX) Starting with the second movement. Watts, Helen, contralto. London Symphony Orchestra.
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Giorno di regno, 10" reel (Box 36, Folder 853)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXI) Pagliughi, Lina, soprano
  - Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Liebe der Danae. Act I, 10" reel (Box 36, Folder 854)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXII) UCLA broadcast performance Members of the University of Southern California Opera Theater. Ducloux, Walter, conductor
  - Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Liebe der Danae. Act II, 10" reel (Box 36, Folder 855)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXIII) UCLA broadcast performance Members of the University of Southern California Opera Theater. Ducloux, Walter, conductor
  - Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Liebe der Danae. Act III, 10" reel (Box 36, Folder 856)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXIV) UCLA broadcast performance Members of the University of Southern California Opera Theater. Ducloux, Walter, conductor
  - Flotow, Friedrich von, 1812-1883. Martha, 10" reel (Box 36, Folder 857)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXV. Taped from discs)
  - Salzburger Festspiele. Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Macbeth 1964, 10" reel (Box 36, Folder 858)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXVI) Bumbry, Grace, 1937-, mezzo-soprano; Fischer-Dieskau, Dietrich, 1925-, baritone; Sawallisch, Wolfgang, 1923-, conductor
  - Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Villi, 10" reel (Box 36, Folder 859)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXVII. Taped from discs) Fusco, Cecilia, soprano
  - Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963. Dialogues des Carmélites. Part I, 10" reel (Box 36, Folder 860)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXVIII) Crespi, Régine, soprano; Duval, Denise, soprano; Gorr, Rita, mezzo-soprano; Scharfey, singer; Opéra de Paris. Orchestre. Dervaux, Pierre, 1917-1992, conductor.
  - Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963. Dialogues des Carmélites. Part II, 10" reel (Box 36, Folder 861)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXIX) Crespi, Régine, soprano; Duval, Denise, soprano; Gorr, Rita, mezzo-soprano; Scharfey, singer; Opéra de Paris. Orchestre. Dervaux, Pierre, 1917-1992, conductor.
  - Paisiello, Giovanni, 1740-1816. Barbiere di Siviglia. Acts I and III, 10" reel (Box 36, Folder 862)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXX) Act II in tape 519
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Matthäuspassion. Abridged version, 10" reel (Box 36, Folder 863)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXXI)
  - Spontini, Gaspare, 1774-1851. Vestale, 10" reel (Box 36, Folder 864)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXXII)
  - Pope Paul V in New YorkOct. 4, 1965, 10" reel (Box 36, Folder 865)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXXIII)
  - Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Salome. Part I Mar.13, 1965, 10" reel (Box 36, Folder 866)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXXIV) Nilsson, Birgit, soprano; Cassel, Walter, baritone; Dalis, Irene, mezzo-soprano; Liebl, Karl, tenor. Metropolitan Opera (New York, N.Y.). Orchestra
  - Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Salome. Part IIMar.13, 1965, 10" reel (Box 36, Folder 867)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXXV) Nilsson, Birgit, soprano; Cassel, Walter, baritone; Dalis, Irene, mezzo-soprano; Liebl, Karl, tenor. Metropolitan Opera (New York, N.Y.). Orchestra
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 36, Folder 868)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXXVI. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 36, Folder 869)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXXVII. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 37, Folder 870)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXXVIII. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 37, Folder 871)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXXIX. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 37, Folder 872)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXXX. Taped from discs)
  - Barrientos, Maria, 1883-1946, soprano and opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 37, Folder 873)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXXXI. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 37, Folder 874)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXXXII. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 37, Folder 875)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXXXIII. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 37, Folder 876)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXXXIV. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 37, Folder 877)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXXXV. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 37, Folder 878)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXXXVI. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 37, Folder 879)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXXXVII. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 37, Folder 880)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXXXVIII. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 37, Folder 881)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXL. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 37, Folder 882)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXLI. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 37, Folder 883)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXLII. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 37, Folder 884)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXLIII. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 37, Folder 885)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXLIV. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 37, Folder 886)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXLV. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 37, Folder 887)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXLVI. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 38, Folder 888)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXLVII. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 38, Folder 889)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCXLVIII. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 38, Folder 890)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCIL. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 38, Folder 891)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCL. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 38, Folder 892)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCLI. Taped from discs)
  - Opera selections performed by various opera singers, 10" reel (Box 38, Folder 893)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCLII. Taped from discs)
  - French Christmas CarolsDec.12, 1960, 10" reel (Box 38, Folder 894)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCLIII. Taped from discs by the Radiodiffusion - Télévision Française)
  - International Concert Hall. Broadcast1961, 10" reel (Box 38, Folder 895)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCLIV) Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Symphonies, K. 16, E? major. Internationale Stiftung Mozarteum Salzburg. Scherchen, Hermann, 1891-1966, conductor -- Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Miroirs. Alborada del gracioso. Concertgebouworkest. Fournet, Jean, conductor -- Oborin, Lev, piano. Khachaturi?a?n, Aram Il'ich, 1903-1978. Concertos, piano, orchestra, D? major. USSR State Symphony Orchestra. Rozhdyestvenski, Gennadi, conductor
  - International Concert Hall. Broadcast. Series VI, Program 121961, 10" reel (Box 38, Folder 896)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCLV) Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Fidelio (1806). Ouverture. Hungarian State Symphony Orchestra. Lehel, György, conductor -- Aldrovandi, Clelia, harp. Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Concertos, organ, orchestra, op. 4. No. 6; arr. for harp. Rome Symphony Orchestra. Freccia, Massimo, conductor -- Prokofiev, Sergey, 1891-1953. Fairy Tale. Moscow Chamber Orchestra. Barshay, Rudolf, conductor; Oistrakh, David Fedorovich, 1908-1974, violin. Concerto, violin, no. 1, op. 19, D major. USSR State Symphony Orchestra. Rozhdyestvenski, Gennadi, conductor
  - UNICEF ConcertNov. 8, 1968, 10" reel (Box 38, Folder 897)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCLVI) Fischer-Dieskau, Dietrich, 1925-, baritone. Bernstein, Leonard, 1918-1990, conductor
  - Tribute to the late Secretary General of the United Nations Hammarskjöld, Dag, 1905-1961, 10" reel (Box 38, Folder 898)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCLVII) Profile -- Funeral ceremonies in Upsala, Sweden
  - United Nations' 30th Anniversary. Part I Oct. 24, 1975, 10" reel (Box 38, Folder 899)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCLVIII) Fischer-Dieskau, Dietrich, 1925-, baritone; Hamari, Julia, mezzo-soprano. Einem, Gottfried von, 1918-1996. An die Nachgeborenen. Cantata composed on commission from Waldheim, Kurt, secretary general of the United Nations -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Symphonies, no. 7, op. 92, A major. Temple University Choir. Wiener Symphoniker. Giulini, Carlo Maria, conductor
  - United Nations' 30th Anniversary. Part II Oct. 24, 1975, 10" reel (Box 38, Folder 900)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCLIX) Fischer-Dieskau, Dietrich, 1925-, baritone; Hamari, Julia, mezzo-soprano. Einem, Gottfried von, 1918-1996. An die Nachgeborenen. Cantata composed on commission from Waldheim, Kurt, secretary general of the United Nations -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Symphonies, no. 7, op. 92, A major. Temple University Choir. Wiener Symphoniker. Giulini, Carlo Maria, conductor
  - Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich, 1840-1893. Pikovai?a? dama, 10" reel (Box 38, Folder 901)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCLX) Arkhipova, Irina, mezzo-soprano. Bolshoi Opera
  - Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Petite Messe solennelle, 10" reel (Box 38, Folder 902)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCLXI. Taped from discs)
  - Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Carmen, 10" reel (Box 38, Folder 903)
    (Fagan's original numbering CCLXII) Horne, Marilyn as Carmen; McCracken, James, 1926-1988 as Don Jose; Maliponte, Adriana as Micaela; Gramm, Donald as Zuñiga; Krause, Tom as Escamillo. Metropolitan Opera House Orchestra and Chorus. Bernstein, Leonard, 1918-1990, conductor
  - Metropolitan Opera House MarathonOct. 1, 1976, 10" reel (Box 38, Folder 904)